## Geoffrey BERGERET French Nationality Driving licence 24 Year old

## "Computer & Network Engineer"

+33 6.51.82.40.48 contact@gbergeret.org www.gbergeret.org

Profile

By experience I acquired lots of skills in several business like: IT Developer, System Administrator or Network Engineer. Now my goal is to specialise myself in IT infrastructure: installation, exploitation, supervision, support and particularly sizing.

**Education & Training** 

2015: Master of Science in Computer Engineer and Network (French Engineer) at ESIPE

Achievements: - transbubbles: Web plate-forme used to translate Comics online.

- dmchecker: Project to apply unit test "JUnit" on Java sources.
- docmycode: Equivalent of "Doxygen" implemented in C for C sources.

2011-2012: Master of Science in Computer Engineer (French Engineer) at UTBM

Left before the end to prioritise professional experience with apprenticeship training.

Achievements: - Implementing a heuristic algorithm.

2011: Two years technical degree in Computer Sciences at IUT in Belfort

Achievements: - TZAAR: TZAAR plate-forme game adaptation in Java.

- Cryptography algorithm implementation in Python(RSA, ElGamal, ...).

Work Experience

Network Engineer (Apprentice) at Orange SA – 09/2012 to 09/2015

Virtual Private Network production automation for business company by some script implemented in Perl.

Network support (second line) for routing, QoS on border side.

System Administrator (Part-time) at SHPS SARL - 02/2011 to 01/2014

Servers responsible : security, installation, automation and technical support (second

level).

Working environment improvement by services deployment like : LAMP, SVN, OpenVPN,

VMware ESXi.

Web Developper (Trainee) at Sales Conquest - 04/2011 to 06/2011

Plugin import/export development for e-commerce website (PHP/MySQL).

Languages Skills

French -> Native

English —> Professional working proficiency (B2 — TOEIC 795)

German —> Elementary proficiency

Technical Skills

Networking: Routing (OSPF, BGP), VRRP, OpenVPN, DHCP, DNS.

Infrastructure: Proxmox, VMWare ESXi, Workstation, Cisco, Firewall (pfsense, ipables).

**System & Scripting**: Linux, Shell (Bash, Zsh), Perl, LAMP, SSH. **Database**: MERISE, ORM, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB.

**Web Developpement**: PHP, (x)HTML, CSS (less), Laravel, Jekyll (Liquid). **Software Developpement**: UML, Java, C/C++, Subversion, Git, Jenkins.

Management Skills

Project Management Conduct training
Facilitate meeting Seminar facilitator

Team organisation

Hobbies

JoggingFitnessMotorcycleTravellingCookingBrunch